{
  "openingRemarks": "Do not bother to simplify the result<br>E.g. can enter \\(\\dfrac{250}{100}\\) as \\(2\\frac{50}{100}\\) instead of \\(2\\frac{1}{2}\\)<p>Also enter \"N\" for any result which is not defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Express \\(69 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(41 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(55 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(48 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(63 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(47 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(59 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(55 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(71 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(62 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(71 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(89 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(79 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(80 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(62 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(53 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 5/6"
    }
  ]
}
